[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "front": "apple",
        "back": "яблоко"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "front": "orange",
        "back": "апельсин"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "front": "driver",
        "back": "водитель"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "front": "designer",
        "back": "дизайнер"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "front": "bath",
        "back": "ванная"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "front": "living room",
        "back": "зал"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "front": "bed",
        "back": "спальня"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "front": "tomato",
        "back": "помидор"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "front": "ball",
        "back": "мяч"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "front": "doll",
        "back": "кукла"
    }
]